// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "what is a BPO??",
    answer: "Business Process Outsourcing",
    options: [
      "Business Process Outsourcing",
      "Business Process Outsource",
      "Business Project Outsourcing",
      "Business Product Outsourcing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What are the factors which have an impact when deciding on a BPO destination?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Reliable telecommunications infrastructure",
      "Cost of labour",
      "Strong regulatory framework",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The most common data conversion options are",
    answer: "Converting raw data into Microsoft Office",
    options: [
      "Converting raw data into Microsoft Office",
      "Convert from PDF to Word",
      "Convert an audio file into text",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The main characteristics of Knowledge Process Outsourcing are?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Process are not easily codified",
      "The agent has to interpret the information",
      "The agent is expected to exercise judgement",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What do you think is the most important justification for a company to consider offshore decision??",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Overall cost reduction",
      "Productivity improvement",
      "Efficiency/Effectiveness",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A TRUE statement between Low End and High End BPO is?",
    answer: "High End BPO have more ruled based processes than Low End BPO and therefore require more skilled manpower",
    options: [
      "Both Low End and High End BPO are mainly Call Centers",
      "Low End BPOs offer relatively much higher salary than High End BPO",
      "High End BPO have more ruled based processes than Low End BPO and therefore require more skilled manpower",
      "People working in Low End BPO companies usually stay much longer in that company than those working in High End BPO"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "BPO companies involved in transcription normally?",
    answer: "Transforming an audio file into text",
    options: [
      "Capture data and translate it into text",
      "Listen to a conversation on-line and translate it into text",
      "Transforming an audio file into text",
      "Translate from one language into a different language"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A BPO company specializing in image processing may provide the following services?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Image Scanning",
      "Image Conversion",
      "Archiving",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In order to improve its global attractiveness index in BPO coming years, India should leverage on its:?",
    answer: "Improving national competencies into global talents",
    options: [
      "Telecom Infrastructure",
      "Skills and competencies of its BPO Workforce",
      "Improving national competencies into global talents",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What does XML stand for?",
    answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
    options: [
      "eXtensible Markup Language",
      "eXecutable Multiple Language",
      "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
      "eXamine Multiple Language"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "In terms of cost characteristics, which of the following are outsourcing location decisions from low cost to high cost?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Overall cost reduction",
      "Productivity improvement",
      "Efficiency/Effectiveness",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Most commonly used databases for making data entry is?",
    answer: "All of the Above",
    options: [
      "Microsoft SQL Server, ASP, Ms Access, Oracle",
      "My SQL, FoxPro, ASP, Ms Access",
      "Oracle, My SQL, FoxPro, Visual Basic",
      "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "what is the THREE PDF formats commonly used in Data Capture/Data Entry Operation?",
    answer: "PDF Formatted Text, PDF searchable image, PDF Image Only",
    options: [
      "PDF Formatted Text, PDF searchable image, PDF Image Only",
      "PDF Acrobat Reader, PDF Acrobat Writer, PDF Scanner",
      "PDF to Word Conversion, Word to PDF Conversion, PDF to Image Conversion",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "who orders BPOs?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Banks.",
      "Wall Street Firms.",
      "Private Mortgage Insurance Companies",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];